《终空》前情提要
Previously on "Final Space"...
银河一号上乱成一团
it's double trouble aboard the Galaxy One
因为总司令和无疆守卫
as the Lord Commander and the Infinity Guard
都把枪口对准了我们的船员
are both gunning for our crew.
小卡多正在拼命地试图联系他的父亲...
Little Cato is desperately trying to contact his father...
哦不！奎恩还正要解开
Oh, no!... and Quinn is about to unlock
威胁地球的巨大谜题
a huge mystery threatening Earth.
哦  双重的“不”
Oh, double no.
光是想想这个  我裤子都绷紧了
My slacks are tightening just thinking about this.
哦  三重的“不”
Oh, triple no.
盖瑞  你还有5分钟氧气可用
Gary, you have 5 minutes of oxygen left.
我之前活得很好
I lived a good life.
中等偏上 有时稍微有点恶心
Medium to good / borderline crappy.
我有次从袖口侧面看到过妹子的大波  棒极了
Saw some side boob once. That was cool.
HUE  你见过“袖口侧面的大波”吗？
H.U.E., have you ever seen side boob?
袖口侧面的大波？我没见过  盖瑞
Side boob? No, Gary.
你说得越多  氧气也就...
The more you talk, the more oxygen you...
你错过太多了  不过可能也没那么糟糕
You're missing out. I guess it wasn't all that bad.
我收回刚刚那句话  我之前活的很好
In fact, I take it back. I lived a good one.
当然了！这是...
Of course! This is...
谢谢了！我的人生烂透了！
Thank you! My life sucks!
鸭嘴兽字幕组出品
翻译 + 校对 + 压制：Kyl
Final Space - Chapter Five
终空  第一季第五集
Sync & Correction by f1nc0 from Addic7ed.com
本字幕仅供学习交流  请于下载后24小时内删除
这就是盖瑞舰长
This is where Captain Gary wields
挥舞巨大的力量权杖的地方
the great giant scepter of power.
你不是舰长  申请通信输出
You're not a Captain. Communication output requested.
申请通信输出？真的吗？
Requesting a communications output, are we?
你真的很知道怎么挑逗我
You really know how to press my buttons.
- 挑逗！   - 呃  那我就
- Press! - Ugh. Let me unpress your button
简单粗暴地告诉你
painfully short and clear.
咱俩之间没有任何可能  绝对没有
It is never going to happen between us. Ever.
这还真是又简单... 又粗暴！
That was painfully short... and clear!
奎恩  为什么你都不肯给我一个机会？
Come on, Quinn. Why won't you give me a chance?
你囚禁了无疆守卫的一员
You impersonated a member of the Infinity Guard
而且炸飞了92艘帝国巡飞舰
and blew up 92 Imperium Cruisers.
你叫我怎么相信你
That doesn't inspire a lot of trust.
那我猜  咱俩之间这份珍贵的情谊
Then I guess this precious thing we have between us
就算是断了吧  我很抱歉
is not gonna work out. I'm sorry.
- “你”竟然和“我”提出分手？   - 奎恩  我们之间结束了
- Did you just break up with me? - Quinn, it's over.
我拔出了丘比特之箭  把它折断
I pulled the Cupid's arrow out, snapped it,
又投进了分手的熊熊烈焰中
and threw it into the break-up flames.
用它烤个棉花糖  继续你的生活吧
Toast a marshmallow and get on with your life.
我没空和你玩这个
I don't have time for this.
我需要进入无疆守卫网络的密码
I need to get the password to the Infinity Guard network.
有人需要进入无疆守卫网络的密码吗？
Does someone need the password to the Infinity Guard network?
- 你怎么知道的？   - 我怎么知道的？
- How did you know? - How did I know?
- 我一直在听   - 真的？
- I'm always listening. - Really?
你能别这样吗  马上停下行不行？
Can you stop that, like, immediately?
我能吗？不  我不能
Can I? No, I can't.
就是这  HUE  放大
There it is, H.U.E. Zoom in.
这个缺口有黑洞的特征
The breach has the characteristics
而且还在膨胀
of a black hole, and it's growing.
你和无疆守卫报告了这个
You told the Infinity Guard this
他们非但不听  还想把你抓起来？
and they didn't listen and they want to arrest you?
他们真是一群大坏蛋
They're total bad guys.
无疆守卫的厨房里  散发出了
That smell coming from the Infinity Guard kitchen?
一盘叫做“腐败大乱炖”的菜的味道！
A little dish I call Corruption Stew!
无疆守卫一点都不腐败
The Infinity Guard is not corrupt.
我懂了  你还在生我的气  因为我提出了分手
I get it. You're mad I broke up with you.
- 我的耐心快用完了   - 快用完了  你个妖女
- My patience is whittling away. - Whittle away, temptress.
你的言语再也无法伤害我了
Your words can't hurt me anymore.
哇  好漂亮！这是啥？
Wow. How pretty! What is that?
等离子态的能量正从那颗行星射出  直接进入了缺口
Plasmic energy is firing from that planet directly into the breach.
如果激光继续照下去  缺口将会扩大
If the laser continues, the breach will widen,
地球将会被吸进去
and Earth will be consumed.
HUE  扫描一下那颗行星上的居住者
H.U.E., scan that planet for inhabitants.
那是无疆守卫的前哨基地
That is an Infinity Guard Outpost.
那味道不是汤  不是肉汤
It's not a soup. It's not a broth.
哦！我知道了  那就是大乱炖的味道！
Oh! [Chuckles] I know. It's a stew!
- “腐败大乱炖”！   - 一定是有个可信的理由的
- Corruption stew! - There has to be a good explanation.
我们过去  HUE  准备光折引擎
We're going. H.U.E., prime the lightfold engines.
喔啊  喔啊  喔啊  喔啊  喔啊！
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
在我们分手的瞬间  控制权就已经回到舰长大人手里...
The moment we broke up, that right went back to el capitan...
- HUE  我们怎么能去那边？   - 需要舰长的巧计才能去那边...
- H.U.E., how do we get to the surface? - ...with a Captain's finesse.
熄掉引擎  像个漂亮的飞鼠一样
Cutting the engines and gliding in
滑翔进去  这可不是个好主意！
like a glorious coasting stealth squirrel was a bad idea!
好消息  如果这是正确的地方  我们已经到达目的地了
Good news. If this is the right place, we're here.
正在评估损伤  导航装置阵列已下线
Assessing damage. The deflector array is offline.
能量电池组已下线  烘焙房已下线
The power cells are offline. The bake shop is offline.
等等！这艘飞船上还有烘焙房？！
Wait! There's a bake shop on this thing?!
阿瓦卡多和我要下去侦查
Avocato and I will scout on foot.
你们其他人留守阵地  修理飞船
The rest of you stay back and repair the ship.
来吧  阿瓦卡多  咱们走  咋了？！
Come on, Avocato, let's go. What?!
如果让我飞速吐露一下真心话
If I could pour a tall glass of truth-juice
奎恩... 我觉得你不信任我
for you real quick, Quinn... I am not feeling the trust.
在这个世界上我只信任三个人
I only trust three people in this world...
我的狗  我的姐姐
my dog, my sister,
还有无疆守卫的每一个成员
and every single member of the Infinity Guard.
你疯了  我的女士  无疆守卫正想把你捉拿归案
You're insane, my lady. The Infinity Guard tried to kidnap you.
他们还想接管银河一号
And they tried to take over the Galaxy One.
而且狗不能算是人
And dogs aren't even people.
我没理由相信你们之中的任何一个
I have no reason to trust any of you,
所以我只和这个真的武装到牙齿的人出去
so I'm going with the guy literally covered in guns.
KVN  好好修船  再有  不许碰我的任何东西
KVN, fix the ship. Also, don't touch any of my stuff.
也不许碰奎恩的  还有阿瓦卡多的  也不许碰饼干
Or Quinn's stuff. Or Avocato's. Or the cookies. Ju...
就... 就别碰任何东西就成  尤其是各种按钮
Jus... Just don't touch anything. Specifically buttons.
更尤其不许碰火焰喷射器
And especially flamethrowers.
不过你得好好修船  修完就去死吧
But do fix the ship, and then die.
听明白了吗？好的  来吧  月饼！
Okay? Okay. Okay, come on, Mooncake!
Wow!
呃
Ugh.
好诶！
Hooray!
看好了
Watch this.
停！不许盯着我们
Stop! Stop staring.
火焰喷射器！耶！
Flamethrowers! Hooray!
我在烧烧烧！
I'm burning things!
等等  什么？啊
Wait, what? Aah.
爸  这是我的坐标
Dad, these are my coordinates.
快来找我
Come find me.
这破东西根本没用！
Stupid thing won't work!
- 勇敢一点   - 嗯？
- Be brave. - Huh?
我们会把你救出来的
We're going to get you out of here.
- 为什么我要相信你？   - 我们有共同的敌人
- Why should I trust you? - We share the same enemy.
我需要给我爸发一条信息  你能帮我加强信号吗？
I gotta send a message to my father. Can you amplify my signal?
这有个发射站  我可以告诉你怎么过去
There's a transmitting station. I can show you the way.
快跑！
Now run!
Chookity.
Ooh!
嘿... 哦！哦  我的天哪！
Hey, man... Oh! Oh, my gosh!
你不用给所有人的脖子都来上一刀的  阿瓦卡多
You just don't cleave everybody in the neck meat, Avocato!
- 什么鬼？！   - 我来给你点忠告  伙计
- What the freak?! - Let me give you some advice, buddy.
- 说   - 如果你想让奎恩信任你
- Yes. - If you want Quinn to trust you,
你需要踏出第一步  用行动告诉她你有领导力
you gotta step up and show her you can lead.
直视她的眼睛
Make direct eye contact,
不要转移视线  直到你用睫毛吻上她的灵魂
then don't let go until you kiss her soul with your eyelashes.
就像这样  太过了吗  还是刚刚好？
Like this. Too much, or just enough?
哦  哇  哦我的天哪！太帅了！
Oh, my wow. Oh, my wow! It's glorious!
- 嗯  你懂了？   - 我懂了  搞定
- Yeah. So you got it? - I got it. It's done.
完全搞定
Done and done.
嗨  奎恩  这样够吗  还是刚刚好？
Hi, Quinn. Too little, or just enough?
啊啊啊！
Ahhhh!
快回飞船上  你可不是受训的士兵
Just go back to the ship. You're not a trained soldier.
- 你... 什么都不是   - 好吧
- You're a... nobody. - Okay.
我可没想到又有一枚伤我心的钢镚
I didn't expect that hurt coin deposit
存到了我的悲伤存钱罐里  我的天哪
in my sadness savings. Good Lord.
盖瑞  我不是不讲理
Look, Gary, I'm not trying to be mean.
万一你受伤或者死了...
If you get hurt or die...
我可承担不起这个责任
Well, that's a responsibility I don't want.
- 这就是事实   - 我无法接受这个事实
- That's just the truth. - I don't accept your truth.
而且这个事实非常不讲理
And that was incredibly mean.
- 我很抱歉   - 我可没觉得你哪里抱歉了
- I'm sorry. - I don't think you are.
你说对了  我一点都不抱歉
You're right. I'm not.
你有一种很可贵的品质  我就喜欢这个
You have a bite to you. I like that.
我保证  你最后会信任我的
I promise, you will end up trusting me.
你还会陶醉于我的帅气之中  因为我会...
And revel in my awesomeness as I...
一记空手斩  干掉这个巨大的...
karate chop this magnificent...
敏捷得让人烦的... 飞虫！
disturbingly agile... freaking bug angel!
我觉得那东西刚咬了我一口
I think that thing just bit me.
- 啊啊啊！   - 我的老天哪！
- Ahhhh! - Holy crap!
那是个美丽的噩梦！是只让人缩小的恶魔！
It's a beautiful nightmare shrinking demon!
啊！
Aah!
去死！
Hoorah!
- 跟紧我  阿瓦卡多！   - 啊！
- Stay with me, Avocato! - Aah!
在找到解药之前  我不会停步的
I won't rest until a cure is found.
- 月饼  带阿瓦卡多一程   - 啊！
- Mooncake, give Avocato a ride. - Aah!
Mmm-hmm!
哇啊！
Whoa!
我来掩护你  月饼！咿呀！
I got your back, Mooncake! Yee-haw!
那是啥？！好像... 好像有条
What was that?! I mean, wha... like a little...
迷你小光波从你的枪里发出来了
a little silly string shooting out of your gun?
你... 这...
Like... I mean, that's...
你... 你到底想些干啥啊？
that's like... What were you even trying to accomplish right there?
哈哈哈  好... 好吧  跟上我！
I mean... Okay, foll-follow me!
蜘蛛！蜘蛛！
Spider! Spider!
有只蜘蛛！
It's a spider!
哦　　蜘蛛！
Ohhh, it's a spider!
啊！哦！
Aah! Oh!
啊！
Aah!
太奇怪了  它说我们在... 这里？
That's weird. It says we're... here?
我亲爱的老天爷哪！你看不见吗？！
Dear Heavenly Lightning Lord! Are you not seeing this?!
- 看什么？呃   - 就在这啊
- Seeing what? Ugh. - It's right here.
看... 这个
Seeing... this.
那他妈是啥？
What the hell is that thing?
你是在说这个巨型激光吗？
Are you talking about the giant laser?
因为如果你说的是这个巨型激光
Because if you're talking about the giant laser,
- 那它就是个巨型激光   - 我知道它是个巨型激光
- it's a giant laser. - I know it's a giant laser.
不过“巨型”这个词远远不能描绘我所看见的东西
Giant doesn't even begin to describe what I'm seeing.
即将启动激光发射
Laser activation commencing.
那就是造成引力干扰的东西
That's what's been creating the gravitational disturbance.
我还以为地球要被吸进黑洞了
I thought the Earth was being sucked
看来是我错了
into a black hole, but I was wrong.
这一切都是精心策划的
This whole thing is being orchestrated...
然而到底是谁策划的？是什么策划的？
By who? Or is it whom?
无论如何  那一定是一个超级混蛋
Either way, it's probably by some serious bad guy.
好一个反转！
What a twist!
为了银河！
For the galaxy!
为了永恒！为了总司令！
For eternity! For Lord Commander!
每一次激光冲击  我们就离终空更近了一步！
With each blast, we get closer to Final Space!
所以  让我们继续吧
So, keep it up.
干得漂亮  杰夫  你带来了很好的消息
Good job, Jeff. Hearing great things.
是！
Yes!
现在告诉我  我他妈要怎么把它关上？
Now, how the hell do I turn this off?
艾瑞克！怎么把它关上？
Eric! How do I turn this off?
是红色的把手吗？往左扳？
Is it the red knob? Do I turn it left?
艾瑞克  别哭哭啼啼了！我直接离开镜头就好
Eric, stop crying! I'm just going to walk away.
是总司令  他接管了无疆守卫
The Lord Commander. He's taken over the Infinity Guard.
- 他们在毁灭地球  他们...   - 他们很腐败！我早就告诉你了！
- They're destroying Earth. They're... - Corrupt! Told ya!
现在  你信任我了吧？
Now do you trust me?
不  现在我唯一能信任的只有我自己了
No. Now I'm the only person I can trust.
你还可以信任盖瑞  你忘了盖瑞了  还有帅比阿瓦卡多
And Gary. You left out Gary. And Hot Wheels Avocato.
在尺寸上所缺的  我会用智慧补回来
What I lack in size I make up for in wisdom.
鉴于你现在这么小个  你是变得和苏格拉底一样智慧了还是怎么着？
So now that you're tiny you're like the new Socrates or something?
总之  上啊  小分队！她需要后援
Whatever. C'mon, squad! She needs backup.
哦  好吧  我猜她不需要
Oh, well, I guess not.
我猜我就坐在这吧唧嘴就行了
I guess I could just sit here and pop my lips.
♪ 炽烈的爱 ♪
♪ Burning love ♪
♪ 炽烈的爱  火热炽烈的爱 ♪
♪ Burning love, hot burning love ♪
♪ 爱  爱  爱  炽烈的爱 ♪
♪ Love, love, love burning love ♪
贝丝  我想让你知道
Beth, I want you to know
这是KVN一生中最愉快的时刻
that this has been the happiest moment of KVN's life.
我从你的脸上也能看出来  我们在一起太快乐了
I can see it on your face. We are so happy.
- 她真性感   - 快停下！
- She is so hot. - Stop!
不许盯着我们  太诡异了
Stop staring. So creepy.
快按我的命令行动！快去修船
Now do my bidding! Fix the ship.
我要杀掉KVN  把贝丝据为己有
I will kill KVN and take Beth for my own.
你想这样  除非先跨过我冰冷的尸体
Over my cold, dead hands.
死亡决斗  我们需要一场死亡决斗
Death fight. We've got a death fight.
呃  我们说到哪了？
Now, where were we?
杰夫是怎么做到的？
How the hell does Jeff do it?
啊！
Aah!
- 呃   - 我告诉过你了  我要自己去
- Ugh. - I told you, I'm doing this on my own.
自己去个大头鬼  不管你喜不喜欢这样  我们是一个团队
The hell you are. Like it or not, we're a team.
没有“我”  就组不成“团队”
And you can't spell "team" without "M" and "E",
“团队”（team）一词的英文有“m”和“e”这两个字母，而“me”意为“我”。
你懂的... 那就是“我们”
and you know what that spells... "Us."
- 成吧   - 好极了
- Fine. - Fine.
一个值得去做的任务  是值得大家一起做的
A job worth doing is worth doing together.
- 谢谢你  阿瓦卡多   - 然而如果队长空谈大话
- Thank you, Avocato. - But a vision becomes a nightmare
队员水平泛泛  美景也能变成梦魇
when the leader has a big dream and a bad team!
好的  好的！闭嘴吧你
Okay, okay! Shut up with that stuff.
我都不明白你在说些啥
I don't even know what you're talking about.
激光将在4分钟后发射
Laser activation in four minutes.
天哪  哦我的老天哪
Geez. Oh, my gosh.
苏比利尔·斯通  那个混蛋
Superior Stone, that bastard.
快点  我们没时间了  我们得赶紧绕过去
Come on, we're running out of time. We gotta go around.
哦  狗带
Ohhhh, crap.
- 啊！激光地狱...   - 嘘！墙很薄的
- Aah! Laser hell... - Shhh! The walls are thin.
别出声  不然他们会听到我们的！
Do not make a sound, or they'll hear us!
你竟然指望我们... 哦！...
You expect us... Ow!...
能从这个通电的痛苦迷宫里爬过去
to climb through this electric pain-maze
与此同时还保持绝对安静？我们又不是魔术师
without making a sound? We're not wizards.
- 啊！   - 求求你们了  能别出声吗！
- Ow! - Will everyone please shut up!
- 啊！   - 好的！那我们就...
- Aah! - Okay! We'll do it your...
哦哦哦！
Ohhhhh!
啊嘎嘎！啊嘎嘎！
Aa-ga-gaah! Aa-ga-gaah!
正中下面的毛
Right on the downstairs mustache.
你难道看不出来现在是最需要保持安静
Do you not see this is the worst possible
- 的时  时  时间... 吗？！ - 我的七舅姥爷啊！
- ti-i-i-ime... for this?! - Tuff titty whompas!
- 都停下   - 舅姥爷！
- Company hold. - Titty whompas!
- 你们听见了吗？   - 听起来像是“七舅姥爷”
- Did you hear that? - Sounded like "tuff titty whompas."
七舅姥爷是他喵的啥？
What the hell is a tuff titty whompas?
- 估计是老鼠发出的声音   - 老鼠会说“七舅姥爷”吗？
- It's probably a rat. - Do rats say "tuff titty whompas"?
大老鼠会说
The big ones do.
哦！
Oh!
哦  我的天哪！啊！
Oh, my God! Aah!
你像是一个小阿瓦卡多的点头玩偶！
You're like a tiny little Avocato bobble head!
啊！
Aah!
警告！有逃犯  封锁起来！
Alert! Escapee. Lock it down!
- 快跑啊！   - 还用你说？
- Now run! - Ya think?
激光将在90秒后发射
Laser activation in 90 seconds.
你们都疯了吗？！
Have you all lost your minds?!
你们在替总司令卖命！我们是无疆守卫啊...
You're working for the Lord Commander! We're Infinity Guard...
我们是整个宇宙最后幸存的希望了
the last vestige of hope in the universe.
你们现在所做的一切将会毁灭地球  我们的家
What you're doing here is going to destroy the Earth, our home.
快住手吧  我在求你们
Stop this. I'm begging you.
- 住手吧   - 说的不错  不过  不会的
- Stop. - That's a good speech, but, nah.
我们不会停下的
Nah, ain't happening.
- 没门！   - 就是  我们不会停的
- No way! - Yeah, no, we're not stopping.
你知道该做什么了  阿瓦卡多  上啊！
You know what to do, Avocato. Hoorah!
我恢复了！哦！耶！
I'm back, baby! Whoo! Yeah!
我被电气化了！
I'm electrified, baby!
喔！杀伤光束启动！耶！哦耶！
Whoo! Murder Beam activate! Yeah! Oh, yeah!
我往上  你往下！好极了！
I go high, you go low! Yes!
耶！盖瑞  你那边怎么样？
Yeah! Gary, how're them guns back there?
非常火辣！
They're hot, baby!
耶！
Yes!
斯通！你个叛徒！
Stone! You traitor!
我所做的一切  都是为了无疆守卫！
What I do, I do for the Infinity Guard!
你个叛徒  内奸  狗贼
You double-crossing sphincter sack.
奎恩  你现在还是可以加入我们的  你差不多是
Quinn, you can still join us. You're just about the only one
唯一一个还没宣誓效忠总司令的了
who hasn't pledged allegiance to the Lord Commander.
别加入  奎恩！别加入！
Don't do it, Quinn! Don't do it!
我们的好日子才刚刚开始呢！
We have such a good thing going here!
我才不加入他们呢  你个白痴
I'm not joining him, you freaking weirdo.
别和他们同流合污！
Don't join forces with this guy!
- 别加入！   - 你为什么要这么做？
- Don't do it! - Why are you doing this?
总司令看到了那边的东西
The Lord Commander has seen what's on the other side.
一旦我们进入终空
Once we break into Final Space,
我们将用光芒点燃整个世界
we'll flood the world with light,
从此以后  再无死亡
and there will be no more death.
那是因为从此以后  连生命都消失了
That's because there will be no more life.
你说的只是第一个阶段  还没到第二个阶段呢
At first. But not at second.
更别提第三个阶段了
And don't even get me started on thirdly.
总之  奎恩  我们还应该谢谢你
Anyway, Quinn, we should thank you.
- 什么？   - 你在酒吧纸巾上写的草稿
- What? - Your scribbling on a bar napkin
让我们终于得以突破量子屏障
allowed us to finally break through the quantum barriers
也因此得以撕开宇宙
and tear through this universe.
所以你看  这其实都是你的功劳
So you see, this is all your work.
开心点
Cheer up.
你不用自责太久的...
You won't have to live with the guilt much longer...
...因为现在  已经没有什么
...because now there's no stopping us
能阻挡我们洞穿终空了
from tearing a hole into Final Space.
激光将在30秒后发射
Commencing laser fire in 30 seconds.
嘿  狗屁叛徒！石头剪刀布
Hey, sphincter sack! Rock, paper, scissors.
我可不玩这个
I'm not playing this game.
很接近了！布！
Close! Paper!
啊！
Aah!
这位老兄被一个巨型老屁眼吸走了
Guy just got sucked into a big ol' butthole.
盖瑞  我们需要干掉那个激光发射器
Gary, we got a laser to take out.
- 好  好  好吧！咱们走！   - 都是我的错
- O-O-Okay! Okay, let's go! - It's all my fault.
- 奎恩  这不是你的错   - 我现在都不能信任我自己了
- Quinn, it's not your fault. - I can't even trust myself anymore.
好吧  你开始钻牛角尖了  似乎还要进行深层
Okay, you're digging deep, and there's some real powerful
自我探索之类的东西
self-discovery stuff going on here,
不过有个巨型激光发射器马上就要开火了
but there's a giant laser about to fire,
咱能不能先放一放这个
so if we could just stick a pin in this
一会吃点心的时候再自我探索？
and pick it up over snacks soon-ish?
激光将在10秒后发射
Laser activation in 10 seconds.
斯通把控制板打坏了  激光已经停不下来了
Stone shot out the controls. The laser can't be stopped.
激光现在发射
Laser activation commencing now.
月饼  把激光发射器打下来！
Mooncake, shoot the laser!
- 你疯了吗？   - 没错！把激光发射器打下来！
- Are you crazy? - Yes! Shoot the laser!
Chookity.
把激光发射器打下来！
Shoot the laser!
Chookity?
把它打下来！
Shoot the laser!
Chookity!
打下来！打下来！
Shoot it! Shoot it!
把它打下来！
Shoot the laser!
Chookity!
哦  我的  老天哪
Oh. My. Crap.
电梯！快点！
The elevator! Hurry!
我的七舅姥爷啊！
Tuff titty whompas!
KVN？HUE？我们需要紧急施救！
KVN? H.U.E.? We need an emergency extraction!
喔啊！月饼！
Whoa! Mooncake!
啊！
Aah!
我们要死了！
We're going to die!
- 除非你信任我   - 对不起  我做不到
- Not if you trust me. - I'm sorry. I can't.
- 我觉得你能做到   - 好吧
- I think you can. - Okay.
好的  别担心  我有这个
Okay. And don't worry. I have one of these.
啊啊啊！
Aaah!
啊！为什么他们给我的机械手
Aah! Why would they connect the nerve endings
还接上了神经？！啊！
to my robot hand?! Aah!
为什么？！
Whyyyy?!
哇啊！
Whoa!
啊！
Aah!
啊！哇啊！
Aah! Whoa!
当我早上醒来的时候  我没有想  “我要死了”
When I woke up this morning, I did not think, "I'm going to die."
不过看看我们  看看我  看看她
But look at us. Look at me, look at her.
我们是一个团队  要死就一起死
Here we are. A unit. Dying together.
哦不  等等！看啊  是银河一号！耶！
Oh, no, wait! Look, the Galaxy One! Yeah!
啊！
Aah!
哦！
Oh!
你成功了
You came through.
我说了... 我们有同样一场战役要打
I told you... we fight the same war.
不过有密码锁
But it's key locked.
是43728
4-3-7-2-8.
我进来了  谢了  我欠你个人情
I'm in. Thanks. I owe you.
爸  这是我的坐标  快来找我
Dad, these are my coordinates. Come find me.
我的意思是  等你有空的时候  不过还是
I mean, at your leisure, but like, for me, preferably fast.
希望你能快点
That'd be great.
然后... 发送！
And... send!
你成功了！成功了！
You did it! You did!
你... 你成功了！
You... You did it!
你把你爸还有月饼都拱手送我了
You sent your father and Mooncake right to me.
不  不  不  不  不——！
No, no, no, no, nooooo!
你... 你在干什么？
What, uh... what are you doing?
从一开始  你说的就都是对的
Starting over. You were right about everything.
我知道  这是我的福气
I know. It's a blessing.
也是我的祸根
And my curse.
如果总司令已经渗透了无疆守卫
If the Lord Commander corrupted the Infinity Guard
那就是说  一个好人都没有了
it means there's no good guys left.
- 不  还有好人   - 谁？
- Yes, there are. - Who?
我们
Us.
Chookity.
健全的人是互相信任的  我们需要更多信任  而非更少
Healthy people trust. We need more of that, not less.
- 我该怎么做？   - 从这里开始...
- But how can I? - You begin right here...
...从这个人开始
...with this guy.
- 我们都是好人   - 好吧
- We're the good guys now. - Okay, then.
- 我们   - 没错  我们
- Us. - Yeah. Us.
哦  KVN！
Oh, KVN!
看在三层地狱的份上  你到底对飞船做了些啥？！
What in the three rings of hell did you do to the ship?!
Sync & Correction by f1nc0 from Addic7ed.com